Guide to the Tamiment Playhouse Records TAM.107
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Music
  - "Gertrude" from Hold Me Hamlet, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - "My Royal Fanny" from Hold Me Hamlet, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - "No One Can Do It Like a Dame" from Hold Me Hamlet, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - "Something Smells in Elsinore" from Hold Me Hamlet, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Utility: "Hamlet Theme", 1956 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - How Do You Like Us, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - I Can't Imagine, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - I Crow, I Roar, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - I'd Better Quit While I'm Ahead, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - I Didn't Even Know, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - If All the Seas were One Sea, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - I'll Be Home Soon, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - I'll Dance You, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - I'm All Yours, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Independence, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - In September by Lucille Kallen & Max Liebman, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Intellectual Rag, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Intoxication, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - I Reach for You, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - I Said to Love, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Isn't She Lovely, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - It Doesn't Cost Much to Live in New York, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - It's Bad for Our Country in the Newsreels, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - It's Simple to be Famous, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - It's Sunday, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - It's Very Funny, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - I've Heard A lot about You, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "I Wonder Why She Couldn't Sleep" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Jonah and the Whale, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Just an Ordinary Morning, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The Kingston Weavers, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Knight to the Rescue, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - "Ladies in Waiting" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lady Chatterley (segue only), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lament on 5th Avenue, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - La Ronde, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Last Two People Alive, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Legit, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Laugh, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Let's Get Together, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Lighted Windows, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Living Statues, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Local, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - London Town, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Loot Song, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Lost, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Love of, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Lullaby of the Nightingale of Samarkand" from Princess & the Pea, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Maggie, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Magical Lima, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - "Mamalogue" from Princess & the Pea, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Math Magic, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Miss Nobody, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Mr. Klein, 1959, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Mr. Spring, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Montreal, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Most Famous Models, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Movie Music (finish), 1954 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "My Dish of Tea" from Jack the Ribber, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - My Romantic Bearded Lady (and my Rubber Man), 1952 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Nanny, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Negative Thinking, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - New Day, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - New Leading Man, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Newsreel, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Nightmares (ballet), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Nightsong, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Night Time, 1951-1952 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - No Fun Trio: Vogue, Esquire, Women's Home Companion, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Nursery Rhymes, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 1/2/03, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Othello, I care (incidental music), 1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Our Eyes Met, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Our Opening, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Overture: 9th Show, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Overture, 1953, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Overture, 1953, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Overture, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Overture, 1954, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Overture, 1955-1959 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Overture, 1958, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Overture, 1956-1959 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Overture 1957, 1957-1959 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Overture 1960, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Pantomime Single, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Papiyo, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Paris Soir, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Partners, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - The Party arranged by Jonathan Tunick, 1959-1960 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Passion, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Pen Pals, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - People Will Talk, 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Places Please, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Playmate of the Month, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - A Popular Song, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Powers of a Woman, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - The Previews, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Price You Pay for the Art, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - "Prologue: Many Moons Ago" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Song of Love [Fred]" from Princess & the Pea, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - "Utilities" for Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Very Soft Shoes" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - "Overture" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - "Wizard" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "Finale" from Princess & the Pea, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Problem, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Published Music, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Pullman Car Opening / On the Isle of Manhattan, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Put It On, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - A Quiet Life, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - A Quonset in Naponset, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Rain, Keep Raining, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - A Really Big Shoe, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Red Hot, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Rinky-Tink, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - The Rubaiyat Revisited, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - School Skit and Garden Skit Lead-ins, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Semper Mary, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Seymour, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Shadow, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Shake Hands With a Millionaire, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Silent World, The, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Silent World, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Small Talk, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Someday I'll Find You (incidental), undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Something Old, Something New, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Song of the Sirens, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - So What, 1953 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Sports, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - S.R.O.: opening, 1955, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Star, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Star Crossed, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Still a Bambino, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Stop the World, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - String!, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - String Quartet, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Subway Music (Incidental), undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Superstitious, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Target for the Cossack at the Kretcma, The, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Tell the Girl (arranger: Hal Hidey), undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ten Past Ten, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - That Great Big Candy Store up in the Sky? (arrranger: Jonathan Tunick), 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - That Moment When, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - That's How I Feel, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Thee on My Mind, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - There You Are, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - There You Are, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - There's Nowhere to Go but Up, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - They, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Thirty Times Three, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Three Echoes, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - "This is My Knight" from Princess & the Pea, undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - This is My Summer, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - This is Why We're Here, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Time, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - The Time Step, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Too Many Questions, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Train De Mystere, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Trials of Tillie, The, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Tunick, Jonathan: Contrasts ballet, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Twinkle, Twinkle, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Two a Day, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Two Moons over Elsinore" Hamlet, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Unexpurgated Version, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Vending Machines, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Versatility, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Waiting to Waltz with You, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Walk Tall, 1954, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - We Played it in the Cellar, 1954, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - When the Saints Go Marching In (Incidental music), undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Whistle Stop, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - William, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - With All Due Respect, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Yesterday I Loved You, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Hollister, David (music) & Don Meyer (lyrics), 1952 (Box 29A, Folder 1)
  - "Panic on Seventh Avenue" (Lee Pockriss, music / Don Meyer, lyrics), undated (Box 29A, Folder 2)
  - "Press" (Goldenberg), undated (Box 29A, Folder 3)
  - "State of the Nation" (Richardson/Rosner), undated (Box 29A, Folder 4)
  - "Time Was" (Fuller/Barer), undated (Box 29A, Folder 5)
  - "Travelin' Man" (Rodgers/Barer), undated (Box 29A, Folder 6)
- Series V: Scrapbooks
  Series V. Scrapbooks, contains of nine volumes of clippings and ephemera, seven for Camp Tamiment and the Tamiment Institute, and two for the Tamiment Playhouse.
  - Scrapbook A: Early Camp PR Materials, 1921-1927 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook B: Camp PR Materials/Programs, 1926-1931 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook C: TPH, 1929-1935 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook D: Camp PR Materials, 1932-1934 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook E: TPH, 1936-1939 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook N: Tamiment Institute Events, 1950-1953 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    General note
    [flat box, 12" x 15" x 3"]
  - Scrapbook P: Tamiment Institute Chamber Music, 1952-1956 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook F: Clippings, Programs, PR Material, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    [flat box, 14" x 18" x 3"]
  - Scrapbook O: Theatre, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook P: Willard Levitas (Scenic Designer) Tamiment Playhouse, 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook Q: Willard Levitas (Scenic Designer) Tamiment Playhouse, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Artwork: "Manhattan Greenery", Willard G. Levitas, June 8, 1950